<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
  <identifier>AgainstTheStateLlewellynH.RockwellJr_201408</identifier>
  <mediatype>texts</mediatype>
  <collection>opensource_media</collection>
  <creator> Llewellyn H. Rockwell Jr</creator>
  <date>2014-06-07</date>
  <description>&lt;div class="descriptionWrapper"&gt;
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Against the State: An Anarcho-Capitalist Manifesto&lt;/em&gt; diagnoses
 what is wrong with the American political system, and tells us in no 
uncertain terms what is required to stop leviathan. Rockwell's 
prescription is &lt;span&gt;radical, calling for the wholesale realignment of society away from the state and toward voluntary order. As the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;book
 incontrovertibly shows, the overwhelming problems that confront us 
today are no accident. They stem from the nature of government itself. 
Only peaceful cooperation grounded in individuals, families, civil 
society, and markets &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;can rescue us from our present plight.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Against the State&lt;/em&gt; applies Murray Rothbard’s unique 
combination of individualist anarchism and Austrian economics to 
contemporary America. Fueled by an out-of-control banking system, the 
American Über-State has become in essence fascist. We cannot escape our 
predicament through limited government or traditional political means: 
government is incapable of controlling itself. Only a purely private 
social order can save us, and Rockwell succinctly sets out how an 
anarcho-capitalist society would work. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 190 short pages, Rockwell has created nothing less than the modern
 manifesto for today's anarcho-capitalist movement. This is the 
must-read book of 2014 for libertarians interested in real arguments for
 creating a peaceful, voluntary, free-market society.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;</description>
  <scanner>Internet Archive HTML5 Uploader 1.5.2</scanner>
  <subject>Capitalism</subject>
  <title>Against The State Llewellyn H. Rockwell Jr</title>
  <subject>Anarchism</subject>
  <subject>Government</subject>
  <subject>State</subject>
  <publicdate>2014-08-09 14:20:54</publicdate>
  <uploader>bostonkid9096@gmail.com</uploader>
  <addeddate>2014-08-09 14:20:54</addeddate>
  <curation>[curator]validator@archive.org[/curator][date]20140809142114[/date][comment]checked for malware[/comment]</curation>
  <language>English</language>
  <identifier-access>http://archive.org/details/AgainstTheStateLlewellynH.RockwellJr_201408</identifier-access>
  <identifier-ark>ark:/13960/t96716z6v</identifier-ark>
  <repub_state>4</repub_state>
</metadata>
